♪ She packed my bags
last night pre-flight ♪
♪ Zero hour, 9:00am ♪
♪ And I'm gonna be high ♪
♪ As a kite by then ♪
♪ I miss the Earth so much ♪
♪ I miss my wife ♪
♪ It's lonely out in space ♪
♪ On such a timeless flight ♪
♪ Ooh...
- And I think it's gonna be ♪
♪ A long, long time ♪
♪ Till touch down brings me
round again to find ♪
♪ I'm not the man they think
I am at home ♪
♪ Aah...
- Oh no, no, no ♪
♪ I'm a rocket man ♪
♪ Rocket man, burning out
his fuse up here alone ♪
♪ And I think it's gonna be
a long, long time ♪
♪ Till touchdown brings me round
again to find ♪
♪ I'm not the man they think
I am at home ♪
♪ Aah...
- Oh no, no, no ♪
♪ I'm a rocket man ♪
♪ Rocket man, burning out
his fuse up here alone ♪
♪ Mars ain't the kind of place
to raise your kids ♪
♪ In fact, it's cold as hell ♪
♪ And there's no one there
to raise them ♪
♪ If you didn't ♪
♪ And all this science ♪
♪ I don't understand ♪
♪ It's just my job ♪
♪ Five days a week ♪
♪ Rocket man ♪
♪ Ooh...
- And I think it's gonna be ♪
♪ A long, long time ♪
♪ Till touchdown brings me round
again to find ♪
♪ I'm not the man they think
I am at home ♪
♪ Aah...
- Oh no, no, no ♪
♪ I'm a rocket man ♪
♪ Rocket man, burning out
his fuse up here alone ♪
♪ Ooh...
- And I think it's gonna be ♪
♪ A long, long time ♪
♪ Till touchdown brings me round
again to find ♪
♪ I'm not the man they think
I am at home ♪
♪ Aah...
- Oh no, no, no ♪
♪ I'm a rocket man ♪
♪ Rocket man, burning out
his fuse up here alone ♪
♪ And I think it's gonna be
a long, long time ♪
[MUSIC FADES]